

NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DUNG NHÂN SỬ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên Tung D. | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn





Tung D.

Fresher Android

Date of birth: Jan 26, 1995

Gender: Male

Phone: [protected data]

Email: protected@topcv.vn

Address: Thuong Tin, Hanoi, Vietnam

Website: [protected data]

OBJECTIVE

I consider myself cautious, friendly, curious, can handle stressful situations well, and have a good critical thinking ability. I like to read, play games, conduct research and seize new things. In my opinion, a programmer is an intriguing career and it will be my passion now and in the future. I want to become a Senior Android developer in the near future.

EDUCATION

Oct 2015 - Jan 2021 Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Major: Electronic And Telecommunication Engineering

GPA: 2.51/4

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 - Present	Hirayama Vietnam Limited Liability Company
	Technical Staff
	- Managing the company's website to sell online courses.
	- Aiding developing online courses for training different companies.
July 2019 - December 2019	CMC Joint Stock Company Develop a telecommunication network
	Technical Staff tuyendung.topcv.vn
	- Participate in the process of supervising and developing a

telecommunication network. M NANC

CERTIFICATIONS

2019 TOEIC Certificate with score 555

SKILLS

Language	English
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint

INTERESTS

I like soccer, music, code...

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Completed the code course of Java Core
- Have knowledge about the OOP
- Completed the code course of Android (Java)